VALORANT_QUOTES = [
                "Are you Cypher? Cause I'd give you my corpse.",
                "Are you Sova? Cause I can't hide from your sight.",
                "Are you Skye? Cause your beauty blinds me.",
                "Are you Sage? Cause your personality heals me.",
                "Are you Reyna? Cause you stole my heart.",
                "Are you Pheonix? Cause you set my passion alight.",
                "Are you Kay/O? Cause I want to pick you up.",
                "Are you Omen? Cause you TPed into my heart.",
                "Are we sure we’re on Haven? Because if you’re here, then I’m pretty sure this is heaven.",
                "If we go in two different directions, my heart will Fracture.",
                "You’re more beautiful than Breeze.",
                "I’m Split between hugging you and kissing you.",
                "I picked Icebox so we’d have a reason to cuddle.",
                "I’d break down the Ascent doors just to see you.",
                "My heart will Fracture if you leave.",
                "…can you Bind me?"] 

OSU_QUESTIONS = osu_questions = [{"question": "Which player achieved the first SS on The Big Black?","answer": "rrtyui"},
            {"question": "What is the highest RPM a spinner can go to?","answer": "477"},
            {"question": "What year did osu first release?","answer": "2007"}, 
            {"question": "What mapper has the most ranked maps?","answer": "Andrea"},
            {"question": "Which featured artist has the highest number of available songs?","answer": "Camellia"},
            {"question": "Which country has the second most OSU World Cup wins?","answer": "South Korea"}, 
            {"question": "What is the current PP record?","answer": "1371"},
            {"question": "What map is the current PP record on?","answer": "Marianne"},
            {"question": "What year did WhiteCat become rank 1?","answer":"2019"},
            {"question": "What keybind hides the replay interface when watching a replay in-game?","answer":"h"},
            {"question": "What is the max combo of the original version of the map The Big Black?","answer":"1337"},
            {"question": "Which player obtained the first 1,000pp play?","answer":"Vaxei"},
            {"question":"What is the song name of the most played osu! map?","answer":"No Title"},
            {"question":"What is the BPM of the map Freedom Dive?","answer":"222"},
            {"question":"What is the BPM of the map Blue Zenith","answer":"200"},
            {"question":"What is the BPM of the map Everything will Freeze?","answer":"240"},
            {"question":"What song has the highest star rating as a loved map?","answer":"The Solace of Oblivion"},
            {"question":"What is the name of the osu!standard mascot?","answer":"Pippi"},
            {"question":"WHat is the name of the osu!catch mascot?","answer":"Yuzu"},
            {"question":"What is the name of the osu!taiko mascot?","answer":"Mocha"},
            {"question":"What country does the .sh domain of the osu website come from?","answer":"Saint Helena"},
            {"question":"What was mrekk's first osu username?","answer":"EliteBrandon365"},
            {"question":"What is the maximum number of friends a player can have on their friend list if they have supporter?","answer":"500"}]    

VALORANT_QUESTIONS = valorant_questions = [{"question": "Which player has been on the team Sentinels the longest?","answer": "TenZ"},
            {"question": "What year was Valorant officially released?","answer": "2020"},
            {"question": "What team won Valorant Champions 2022?","answer": "Loud"},
            {"question": "What team won Lock//In Sao Paulo?","answer": "Fnatic"},
            {"question": "Who is the IGL for Team Heretics?","answer": "Boo"},
            {"question": "Who is the IGL for 100 Thieves?","answer": "Boostio"}]